https://www.furrycritter.com/privacy.htm

Your Privacy
The Furry Critter Network is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of The Furry Critter Network. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. This policy deals mainly with user interactive features that may again be enabled.
What personally identifiable information is collected from you?
The The Furry Critter Network collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site. Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, we ask for your name and email address. The system will also ask for your street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, telephone number, and the URL of your web site, although only fields that are marked with an asterisk (*) on the registration field are required. This information is used solely to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms (such as the ad posting form) with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to The Furry Critter Network - you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of The Furry Critter Network. In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place ads or take advantage of the other features of The Furry Critter Network (this feature was removed in May 2006 but may return in the future). If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
What cookies are and how they are used.
As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, The Furry Critter Network may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Several features of The Furry Critter Network require that you accept cookies in order to work properly.
What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information
Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes:
(1) To identify and label all "new" ads since your last visit to the site.
(2) Optionally to permanently save your password on your computer so ou don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.
(3) To enable you to "checklist" ads that you want to mark for future retrieval and viewing.
Advertising networks that serve ads onto The Furry Critter Network may also use their own cookies. The The Furry Critter Network may also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers.
How your information is used
The primary goal of The Furry Critter Network in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout The Furry Critter Network.
Who is collecting your information
If you are asked for personal information on The Furry Critter Network, you are sharing that information with The Furry Critter Network alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of The Furry Critter Network. For example, when you enter personal information on the ad posting form (this feature was disabled in May 2006 but may return in the future), this information will generally be included in your ad, unless specifically stated otherwise.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content
(e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content
from other websites behaves in the exact same way as
if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies,
embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your
interaction with that embedded content, including tracking
your interaction with the embedded content if you have
an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
General traffic statistics are provided to advertisers and/or sponsors when requested. The data captured for this purpose does not include any identifiable personal information.
Who we share your data with
As a general rule, The Furry Critter Network will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared.
The Furry Critter Network may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of The Furry Critter Network or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of The Furry Critter Network, other users of The Furry Critter Network, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. The Furry Critter Network may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.
